Name: Doraemon
(Special Vision Report)
Dady, you know
Please, dady
You're so annoy
How did you know dady
I don't know
Why did you litter everywhere
Go clean up
I've turned my room up side
down for it
Maybe you lost it somewhere out there
Or I left it somewhere and forget
If I don't have that, I'll die
Calm down
You're are a boy
don't be so panicking
What did you get lost this time?
You lost your money
you've tried so hard saving it
You lost all of them ?
How about mine? You
promised to keep for me
Did you lost them too ?
How are you going
to compensate me?
I don't care
I don't care I don't care
Calm down
You're so embarrassing
Where did you lost it?
Think Hurry
Try to remember
I'm not out yet today
I must have lost it yesterday
But I don't remember what
did I do yesterday
Forgetful
Idiot
Any way, I'm an idiot
Doraemon, any machine
to help me remember
Certainly!
The Special Visible Report
The machine will call out vision
From your memory
You went out at around 2:30
yesterday afternoon
Starting from step out of the door
You turned right and then where ?
Just fooling around without any purpose
You looked around
seems so uneasy
Something on the ground
It's candy
Ah, you picked it up
you're so nasty
It's empty.
Disappointed ?
Nobody asked you to pick up
Be quiet, don't be nagging
We're looking for cues
of the money
For sure we'll watch together
Dog fights
Why were you so curious ?
Please, you are so noisy
You're so concentrated
The dog's watching you
What is this ?
After you fell
you blacked out
Maybe you lost the money
at that time
But I bottened up all my pocks
Impossible
Too dumb
Rats
I went to places
Can't find it
You may it at any places
Nobita, '(fling is here
Are you watching 8mm video ?
I want to watch too
But this is no good
This is where we got
together yesterday
When did you shoot this ?
Where did you hide the camera ?
Oh, how disgusting
I introduced you both
My girl cousin visiting
my house
She is pretty
What is this ?
You only film her
You only met once
and you like her so much
It's not what you see
You're so disgusting
Oh, no Shizuka
See, I walked away again
And stopped
what were you doing ?
What was I doing ?
How can you invite me over
to watch this
Shizuka please wait
Doraemon
it's all you fault
Where is the money ?
What? Home already ?
So, you didn't bring money out
when outside
Where did you loss money
any way?
Watch again
From the start till we
just watched
When I walked out my room ?
I called you
And said it wouldn't be
any good if you lost it
Wow, you keep the money for
us, I remember now
Hey, you are the big
forgetful mind
(Human Remote Control)
Everybody is too relaxed
Look at what we got for
the game today
Keep like this, performance
this year's so obvious
Only me the best
And you're all dummies
You can't win like this
I decide to you better be in
special training
From now on,
practice until dark
No one can cut short
and run home
Coach, I need to go to Busiban
I have promised
Doraemon too
It seems not so clear to you
Let me put it this way
I know now
Practice is so fun
SO happy
Can't understand what's in
their minds
Nobita
it's time to make the air plane
Stop playing Baseball now
Hey, we both want to be safe
better wait until we get home
Nobita, what's on your mind
it's still early
More more ball
Come on, come on, come on
You're too slow, move fast
Hey, guys in the front
Step back, step back
Move ahead, step back...
That's it, I see
Human remote control
This the start
Receiver hold
Direction stick
Speed adapter
Auto control
Antena
Let's start testing
To the left first
Straight ahead
Ah? Ah? Ah?
Wow
Move straight ahead
Jian has left
we can stop now
Ya, great
Human remote control is so cool
Let me borrow it
This is straight ahead
This is even more fun than air plane
Right
Ah? What happened?
Am I crazy ?
You've moved too fast
Stupid, let me do it
It's ok, it's ok
Ah? Ah? Ah?
This is for the slow motion
Let me do it this time
Wait, let me play again
I thought there're something
since just now
It's really you guys
Ah, no. He found out
Back, back
Ah? Ah?
What in the world...
You take me as a toy,
how dare you
He's coming after us again
What? Can't catch up at all !
Now we can't control it
to stop
I won't forgive you
I'll beat you up so sadly
I'll get you for this
Forget it
Or his revenge will be terrible
I do this just for you
Right, let's change it into
auto control
I'll beat you up into meatballs
Where did he go ?
Don't know, leave it all
to machine
What would it turn out?
Don't know, leave it to machine
Not my responsible
This is to punish Jian's
violent abuse
Help, Momi
I think he's quite a pity
Last time he got us all
so miserable
Never mind it, all right
let's go home
Sorry, I left during practice
Please forgive me
Who is that? Why so noisy
Jian
I'll let you borrow my comics
please forgive me
What?
Fire ?
You're wonderful
the child called the police
Who's child ?
Don't know
reporters are looking for him
You are the one found
the fire, right ?
Yes, what do you want?
Because you called in time
and stopped a disaster
Where do you live
Can you tell us your name ?
We want to put your story on
newspaper tomorrow
My name is Jian
Lala
I's not on purpose
you can ask Doraemon
Buster
You've come back in time
to help out at the store
One two One two
Wait, don't go
Mom, ask Doraemon
How can you leave your mom
like this, stop there
Jian is still fooling around ?
It'll never end
let's stop here
Be brave and apology to Jian
He shouldn't have tried
to get us killed
Nobita
He's here
Where are you going ?
We want to go to your house
To apology to You
What did you say ?
Apology to me ?
I'm sorry
Please forgive us, will never
do that again
Why don't you use
remote control
I think it's interesting
Let's use it again
Just once more
I like to be remote controlled
How can it be like this?
Didn't you said
you want to revenge
We didn't want to
cause any trouble
Bye now
Too tricky, don't run away
wait
Keep on remote control me
Do it again
we'll never do that again
I like to walk around
aimlessly
Why ?
Because, it's not all Dola A
Dream's fault
How can you do that ?
Please !
(Disgust Maker)
So noisy, be quiet
I'm taking a nap
Don't be so annoying
Nobita
you're always taking a nap
Nobita Suneo is here for you
I'm taking a nap
tell him to come later
You don't often have friends
visiting, go play with him
Go, go, go Huffy
Be careful
This way I can read comics
What's wrong anyway
Jian said he's got something
interesting for us to see
Let's wait here
Here he is
Jian, did you say something
interesting ?
This is a secret
Let me tell you, something
in the box
Right?
What it is ? Let me see
All right, then I'll show you
See
What?
Throw the worm on you ?
When everyone see your face
they'll laugh so hard
But, it's just worm
you're so embarrassing
Can't say that
I've always hated worm
You hate so many things
Worms, grapsupper, snak, spider
And...ah...
Ghost, earthquake, fire, mom
and teacher
You're too much
Nobita, you're a man
you should be brave
Need to be strong to tolerate
things you dislike
That is a true man
Like me
Ah, rat
I hate rats
Help, it's so horrible
Rats, rats...
Can't help it
Everyone hates something
You just can't help that
Can't help it, then
revenge to Jian
What is this?
Disgust Maker
Machine that makes Disgustions
For instance
Write 'Nobita' on board here
Then here...
Come eat desert
You two can share
Red bean cake is my favorite
Looks so delicious
I'm going to eat now
Nobita wait
Doraemon, how long do you
want me to wait?
Now you can eat
I'm going to eat now
Yak, how terrible
I'm so scared of
red bean cake
Do something
I'm so afraid of it, no !
Then I will eat them all
Very good
See
Just use this
the disgustion maker
Good, Jian's so proud
He's not afraid of anything
This time I'm going show him
just wait and see
Then write on the board here...
Better write something common
Ok
This is very interesting
What? I want to see
Even if it's a worm
I won't be scared
Not that kind of thing
Ok, then show me, take it out
This
So lovable, let me hold it
Puppies are my favorite
Jian, what's wrong, why
you're trembling
Pupy is so horrible
What's happening ?
Cool !
That would teach him a lesson
Nobita telephone
Coming
Hello hello
Nobita, you tricked me
Next time when I see you
I'll get you for this
You better keep this in mind
What am I going to do ?
Jian is furious
What am I going to do?
Got it
Erase this first
Then put this on
Nobita, go home hurry
Jian's looking for you saying
he'll kill you
Too late
Not thing to do with me
I'm going to revenge for
what you just did
All right go ahead
No, don't come near me
Horrible Help
Come hit me, come if you dare
Made it, cool
Really so funny
This way Jian will be quiet for
a while
Then I can take a nap
Nap again
Ok...
Horrible How horrible
I'm so afraid of napping
ah, no
So, Nobita
no matter what, still napping
(Child of Typhoon)
All right, get in the house
So nice
Yes, I raise it from an egg
No matter what animal
As long as you care with love
it'll be very close to you
That's true
I want to take care of egg
Care about it with love
Copy cat
Ah...
Can't remember it
What kind of egg is this ?
It's not important
Give me, hurry
I want to take it
I've to say first, no matter
what you'll love it
Don't bully it
I know I know
What kind of egg is this
any way ?
Nobita
Not feeling well?
Want to hatch an egg?
Your mom doesn't want you to
keep animals
Get rid of it right away
It's ok, learning how
to love is good
It's good for Nobita
growing up
Honey, you are really...
What is this?
I remember
Don't hatch that egg
Good boy
Doraemon, I don't know
what is this
But it seems to like me
very much
Liking you is ok
but that is an egg of typhoon
Typhoon's egg
Typhoon is hatched from egg
No, not really
It's the result of the research
by future scientist
It's dangerous, throw it away
No, it's not easy to hatch
We should love and raise it
But typhoon is dangerous
Doraemon, didn't you say
One can't throw away
things randomly
I did say that
Typhoon eats hot air
Wait, let me give you a name
You're child of typhoon
Let's call you phoon
Good, come eat
Look at that
Don't feed it too much food
it'll be a big trouble
Can't help it, it's so cute
Come Phoon
Come here, come here
Watch now, I'll throw the stick
you go fetch it back
Understand
Go
So smart
Nobita, it seems so fun
I want to play too
Yes, ya
You know what would happen for
not listening
How can it be
Phoon
Help
Good job Phoon
Just like this, and teach them good
Help
You bully me
Phoon won't forgive you
So cute
It's always with me
kind of annoying
Last night you're...
Want to cover with blanket?
Phoon, look at you
That's it
Phoon is so cute
She'll stick with me too
Don't be so nasty
Nobita
Mom and dad looking for me ?
They want you to go home
at once
Sorry, got to go now
We'll continue later
Hey, you'll be the defense
Leave at half time, too much
Did phoon make this
That thing is too much
Throw those weird thing away
Come, let's walk in the air
When she's playing
Don't come near, no
Please, I teach her to listen
Keep it in the closet
Please
I know, you win
8 o'clock News
First, is the typhoon news
Super typhonn number 10
Unavoidably coming through Japan
The following are the damaged areas
It will come here soon
That's terrible
Honey
you haven’t fix the broken roof
If typhoon comes
The roof will be blown away
Black out
The wind gets stronger
Phoon is moving violently
in the closet
Be good Phoon
Where are you going, Phoon
Phoon
Phoon...
Come back
It's been an hour
Phoon is not back yet
News break
A small typhoon just occurred
Bumped into the super typhoon
We phoon
This is rear
Two typhoon stick together
Phoon you must win
Electricity is back
Win stopped, hony
Two typhoons are disappeared
Cool
Recently seldom see hony
to be in a such hurry
Did I
So lucky
Phoon
Wait, Doraemon
What?
When I see small current air
Always remind me of Phoon
(Unexisting Shower)
Fly, fly, little bird
fly high
Fly, fly, while cloud
Win, leaves shaking
in the win
The weather is so nice
What a pity to stay home
Guess everyone is playing
outside
Pitcher throw the ball
Player is Doraemon
Ah, it's a hit
Right on the heart of ball
Ball flys so high
Doraemon is chasing
after the ball
Roll on the ground, catch the ball
Perfect performance
You're not going out?
Never
You're going to resist
till the end ?
Guess it'll be difficult?
Mom will ask me to go get
something
Dad said the it's nice out
go play
It's so nice out
don't stay in
Go help with your mom
Hurry
Why not going out
Nobita where are you going
Don't hide in the closet
Nobita
They give up and leave
Why don't you go out
and play
Even if fire, earthquake
or thunders
I'll never go out
Tell me why ?
My friend had an accident
and is in the hospital
After I went to see him
on my way home
Jian said
He' s got an idea
What Jian thinks
usually is bad
Accident can be avoid
We need to traing for it
That's true
When car is about to hit you
Move and jump away quick
How do you train that ?
If you try to hit someone
suddenly
If he couldn't get away
means he's not alarmed
Interesting
Let's find a chance
to beat Jian
No
Everyone is aiming at me
You're always so cowered
No not in the shower
Let the light turn this way
Put the light on
Ok, if you dare, just beat me
Really
Then...
Actually, I'm not there
I'm really here
On the right
Really, this is the true
Doraemon
This is real me
Doing out of the shower, and then
The light will turn to your eyes
You'll see the light
Actually, it's not in
that position
Use the shower and get back
to what it was
This way you don't have
to worry of getting hit
Want to try
Ok, ok
Everyone hit each other
This training is hurting
I think I loss
Everyone's very careful now
no fun
Where is Nobita
Hiding up is too tricky
Here he is
Same old look, very easy
I'll get him first
I will
Be quite, you guys
Nobita is for me
Damn
I'm really here
I'll fix Jian
Hurts, so hurt
What is happening ?
Hurts
Did you do it
You do it
Damn, you trick me
Then, everyone decided to
give up
So, it's all Jian
And his suggestion's fault
Cool
Time to get up
Honey, come here and look
What? Why at this hour
Look
Sleep on the hallway
Look at this kid
So sleep)!
Nobita, go back to your bed
Ah, right, the cleanser
(Predicting Bug)
What, not feel happy ?
Something bad's
about to happen
My eyelids is trembling
This is a sign of bad luck
You're saying it again
not like a child
Don't forget about that
Go play
My prediction is always right
Feeling something bad
is about to come
You're not having
bad luck
Do you know, lauching can
get lucky
Open heart
everything will be fine
Nervous like you will cause
bad luck
Nobita, it's nice out
come out to play
See, I was beaten up
My predict was right
We should study and
live quietly
Can't understand these people
Horoscope?
I was born in 7th of August
A Leo
Let's see
It's a lucky week this week
Good luck with money
Powerful strength
Good relationship with
opposite sex
Really
What happened to you ?
I feel something good is
about to happen
Super
Give you a tool to make
everything good
Predict bug
Predicting thing will happen
The bug will stop on your head
Then?
Then, your prediction will
come true
I predict something
good will happen
Ah, stopped
Something good will happen
Try to think of something
good
Money will drop from
haven
Nothing dropped
Of course
No such thing in the world
Should not
Even you don't believe it
it wouldn't work
Should of something
may come true
I feel I'll find some money
Just this much should be ok
Money, money...
Found it
The prediction come true
It's only 10 Yen
That means your confidence
is insufficient
You just have to keep
an happy hurt
There will be something nice
Ah, hide
What happened?
Why did you hide ?
It's Jian
Look at his expression
Look so mean
He must be in a bad mood
Don't get near him
No use
Why ?
When having good luck, let's go
try it out
Right, horoscope says so
I'll be in good luck this week
Perhaps I will win
Right, be confident
more confidence
I'll being winning
Good, we'll see
Good, Nobita Go for it
Right in time Nobita
I'm not in a good mood
Be confident
You'll be good luck today
Right, this is the lucky week
Hurts
Cool, one punch to knock
down, Nobita
You can make it
if you want to
I feel I can do anything
The horoscope says this week
I've good relationship with
girls
What kind of girls?
I think Shizuka
maybe like me
That is impossible
What do yo mean?
Must be something you have
confidence in
I really do believe
lam so sure
Nobita
Shizuka
I'd like to ask a favor of you
Ok, just say it, don't be shy
Ah, wait
What is that look?
Let's talk somewhere else
With Doraemon here, we can't
talk Let's go
I don't think so
Shizuka, it's only me here
you can say whatever you want
Nobita, you are so weird
Well
Comic books you borrowed last week
give them back to me
Sorry
I's thinking to give them
back to you
Last week?
So, the horoscope I read
from the comics
ls from last week also
Would you please
I knew it
there's no such good things
Nobita, what? Did she say
she like you?
Must having bad luck
this week
I feel something bad's
going to happen
Be open minded
Nobita
Coming
You hit my back, how dare you
That makes us even
I predictin come true
Nobita are you all right?
That's why I said I should
stay home and study
I know, I know
Hurry home
You found 10 yen
that's good enough
It's gone
Right
When Jian beat you up
You lost it, must be it
Can't find it
Someone must pick it up
This week is a bad luck week
Only 10 yen
To me it's big money
I'd better go home soon
Or don't know what'd happen
next
Go home
Hope to be at home safely
Please think not-so-good
things
Hope not to get in the rain
If you think like this
it'll truly...
It really rains
See
Really, it's raining
Why, why did you think
like this
Can't you think of something
better?
But the predict bug
Whatever you predict is
your freedom
Don't get me in it
(Wonder rope)
Let me see
When we go out
Ok, like this
Everyone will be surprised
Nobita
It's Shizuka
Hey, Nobita
Someone disgusting is
with her too
We want to take a ride
Nobita do you want
to joint us?
No, I don't want to
I'm busy
ls it? Too bad
It's a nice weather
to ride a bike
Don't listen to him
Nobita can't ride bikes
No such thing
Then show us
I'm not feeling well today
Excuses
Leave him alone
Let's go
Don't get in the way
Sorry Nobita
get away
Wait Shizuka
The bleeze on my face...
Go and see
I'll surprise everyone
Task good
Hey, anything Nobita
There's only one
It's ok, Doraemon
I'd like to ask you a favor
Please, be still
Ok, like this
Right
Ah, kick it, it'll go
All right
Then let the rope down
What are you doing?
Hurts
Riding horse
You can't even ride a bike
how can you ride a horse?
Listen to me
Why can't ride a bike
Because it's only two wheels
it'll imbalanced
Horse has four legs
so it's easier
Take Doraemon for
practicing
When you get familiar
you can try on machine horse
Nobita is so cute
Perhaps like this
Doraemon bring out
the horse
Your motivation is not right
Machine horse
Got it
Wonder Rope
No matter dogs or cats
Just put on this rope
They'll have the power like horse
For example
Got it
Come Suneo
Excuse me
please help me a little
Want to sit on it?
It seems to collap
No problem
Go, run, run
Right, run
Just like riding a horse
So simple, so easy
Hurts
Are you all right?
I don't cat, I want a dog
Need to find some new once
I got it
He doesn't seem happy
No problem
Just think you're the cowboy
I'm not sure
Help
Don't move
Think of some way to
quiet it down
Ah, no
That's why I say no
It hurts...
Are you all right?
Nothing more common?
Let me think
Got it
Shizuka's Peilo is very nice
Got it, I got it!
Must be successful this time
It's moving, I can't sit
Can't do it
Hold it for me
Stop
Why bully Peilo
I did not bully it
Just want to ride it
like a horse
T
That is
Couldn't be
It's Suneo and Jian
Stop, stop, stop
We found something rare
Dogs and cats with rope
So cool, right?
Just like riding with wind
cool !
Cool, I want to try too
Peilo has rope on too
Real!
Just like riding a horse
So, as I said at the start
Use Doraemon to practice
Wait until you're familiar
with it
I know it !
Pony run run run
(Slowly, panicking)
Doraemon
this is your favorite
No, I don't want to help you
How did you know?
Shame of you
You do the same everyday
Because if you don't help
I can't finish
Really
Why did it turn out to be
like this?
You didn't even think
about it Why not?
You should think about it completely
Yes, why is it like this?
Let me think about it
This is not working
You're too relaxed
That is slow mover, a slower
What you should do
you need to finish it fast
I'm naturally slow mover
So...
Take this, this is speed up
Once you take it, the movement
and feeling will speed up
This is slow
opposite to speeding
Hurry and take it
Ok, I'll take it later
Take it now
I hate taking medicine
It's good for you Don't run
You take it first
Good
Da
What Da?
Too much trouble to say Nobita
Be quiet
finish the home work
I want to write it slowly
Hurry and finish it hurry up
Can't go yet
I've something to ask about
Then hurry
Why so in a hurry?
Life should take your time
Welcome back
I'm just leaving
Huff)'
Hurry and solve the problem
Hurry
why are you so slow ?
Please be seated
take off your shoes
Making tea ? Thank you
Hurry hurry
I'm taking it with me
Drink it fast!
Finish the sweet potato?
Then bye!
My thing is not finish yet?
What?
What are you doing ? Hurry
Don't look at me like that
I move very fast
I realise the effect of pills
Please, forgive me
Please take slow pill
to return to normal, ok?
Take it or not?
I'll take it
Good, then I'll find slow pill
Found it, here
Did you mix up
This is slow pill
Give it to me hurry
Doraemon, slow down
I know, give it to me
Once start running
I can't stop it
Hurry and catch me
What're you doing so slow
Wait, wait
Can't do this
I need to take speeding pill
This is speeding
this is slowing down
Only fools make mistakes
I made a mistake
Speeding pill is here
Mixed up
Just leave it alone
Got to be some way
Help me Nobita
What was that ?
Mom, is Nobita back yet?
ls he back yet?
Not yet
Really
Ah, no I'm so tired
but I can't stop
If not take the slow pill soon
I'll be broken
I won't fall behind snail
Don't look at me like that
I move very fast
What are you doing?
Race
Race ?
Yes
I raced with snail
I loss
You're faster
Hey,hey, he)'
Tell me
What?
Did you see Nobita
Tell my hurry
Can't wait no longer
I said he was there
I can't hear you
I'm home
Nobita what are you doing
at the door
He's waiting for someone
to open the door
Really
What is this?
Candy looks delicious
I'll have some
That is
What?
Hurry, hurry "P
Say it, hurry
Too late
So sorry
The effect of pill is gone
I even went to Chinsen
Doraemon, I have recovered
Hurry and do your home work
How disgusting
That's why I hate to take medicine
It hurts
It hurts, help